Sincro: wyxchari
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
我们溜出去, 看看能不能找到其他的年轻人. 快来
We slip away and see if we can find
all these young people. Come on.
啊, Blade 机长, 我们正在按你的指示
Ah, Captain Blade, we're following your instructions,
寻找住宿中心呢
We're looking for the accommodation centre.
我的指示对你们不适用
My instructions don't apply to you.
你俩不再需要住的地方了
You two won't be needing living space.
Blade 机长, 这是什么?
Captain Blade, what is this?
我搞不懂了, 我们是要留在这里的, 对吧?
I don't understand. We're here to stay, aren't we?
是的, 你们要留在这里, 不过不是以现在的形态
Oh yes, you're here to stay - but not in your present state.
很是抱歉, 但我还是没搞懂你的意思
I'm very sorry, I simply don't understand what you mean.
我跟医疗中心核对过了, 你俩都是人类
I checked with the Medical Centre. You're both human.
我们期望你们是完好无损的, 所以放你们过来了
We want you intact. That's why I allowed
you to come here.
我要你们的脑子
I want your brain.
我跟你说过了, 我不知道他们在哪里
I've told you, I don't know where they are.
你在我这里纯粹是浪费时间
You're wasting your time with me.
我觉得他说的是实话
I think he's telling the truth.
恐怕是这样, 带他出去!
I'm afraid he is. Get him out of here!
他们肯定在这里某个地方
They must be here somewhere.
这个地方我们都搜遍了
We have completely searched this area.
我现在已经安排了50个人搜这一片
I've now got fifty men going through this part
伦敦警察厅也正派人来帮忙
and the Metropolitan Police are sending help.
但时间已经不多了, 还必须搜遍整个机场
But time is running short.
I have to cover the entire airfield.
我现在需要志愿者!
I need volunteers now!
给我接广播室
Get me the public address room.
Heslington, 让所有入岗航班改道
Heslington, divert all in-bound aircraft.
广播室, 这里是总指挥
Public Address Room, this is the Commandant.
把我切到广播系统
Switch me through to the P.A. system
并且在收到下一步指示前, 暂停所有其它广播
and stop all other announcements until further instructions.
我是机场总指挥
This is the Airport Commandant speaking...
请大家注意
Please pay attention.
我要所有机场人员协助执行一项特别任务
I want all available Airport personnel
to assist in a special duty.
请各位到机场警局报告, 他们会给出具体指示
Will they please report to the Airport Police,
who will issue instructions.
同时我也向各位乘客保证, 没有必要惊慌
I would like to assure passengers
that there's no cause for alarm,
并且很抱歉地通知大家, 所有出港航班暂停起飞
and to apologise for the temporary suspension
of all outward flights.
噢
Oh.
你想在这里达到什么目的呢?
What did you hope to achieve here?
求你给个机会, 为了五万年轻人的性命
A chance to plead with you
for the lives of fifty thousand young people.
他们只不过是人类
They're only human beings.
那你们是什么?
And what are you?
我们是宇宙中最智慧的种族
We are the most intelligent race in the universe.
- 总管?   - 什么事?
- Director?  - Yes?
夫里堡的航班刚刚起飞了
Freiburg flight has just taken off.
为什么, Jamie!
Why, Jamie!
- 你想同我说话?   - 噢不想, 当然不想
- You wish to speak to me?  - Oh no, of course
你...你不是 Jamie, 你是个变色龙
It's... it's not Jamie. You're a Chameleon.
不过, 我觉得你扮他扮得并不好
Well, I don't think you've done a very good job on him.
- 怎么不好?   - 在转换过程中你丢掉了他的苏格兰口音
- Why not?
- Well you lost his Scots accent in the processing.
我还是更喜欢原装的
Oh I much preferred the original.
博士, 如果你是在找你朋友的原身, 在这里是找不到的
If you're looking for your friend's original,
Doctor, you won't find it in here.
- 真的吗?   - 找不到, 它在...
- Really?  - No, it's...
...一个安全的地方
...in a safe place.
离这里并不远. 我们还等什么呢?
Not far from here. What are we waiting for?
杜布罗夫尼克和雅典, 我们的人还在等着去接
Dubrovnik and Athens.
They're waiting to collect our personnel.
我们比计划提前了好多, 可以等
We're well ahead of schedule. We can wait.
继续, 开始转化
Proceed with the processing.
对了, Blade 队长, 恭喜你把这个人带到这里来了
By the way, Captain Blade,
congratulations on bringing this man here.
我将亲自决断我们中谁将获得他的身份
I personally will decide which of our people
is to have his identity.
肯定是你的朋友中的某位, 毫无疑问
It'll be one of your friends, I've no doubt!
这是可以理解的...
Well it's understandable.
留在上面的这些特殊的人会有更多的安全感
The special people up here feel more secure
因为他们的原身就在卫星里面
if their originals are actually in the satellite.
- 闭嘴  - 总管没有什么需要担心的
- Be quiet.  - The Director has nothing to worry about
因为他的原身, Crossland 督察, 的确就在卫星上
because his original, Detective Inspector
Crossland is actually on board.
但是, 你的原身在哪里呢?
But, where's your original?
还有你的?
And where's yours?
够了! 他们的原身都非常安全
That's enough! Their originals are perfectly safe.
藏在盖特威克机场一个地方, 他们永远找不到
Hidden on Gatwick Airport, where they will never be found.
你说我们的原身是什么意思?
What did you mean about our originals?
哦, 据我的观察, 你们分两类
Well, as I see it, there are two categories.
一类是跟你们总管和那边那个人一样...
People like your Director and that man over there...
....原身就在这里, 很安全
..whose originals are safe on board here.
另一类就是跟你们俩一样
And then there are people like you two,
原身被留在盖特威克机场
whose originals have been left behind at Gatwick airport.
如果原身被搞坏了...你们就完蛋了!
If they're tampered with... you're finished!
他在撒谎
He's lying.
快点, 赶在总管回来之前, 把他装进机器里去
Come on, let's get him into the machine
before the Director returns.
好, 你最好快点把我转化掉
Yes, you'd better process me quickly,
要不然你俩随时都会不存在了
because any minute now you'll cease to exist.
你是名单上的第一个!
You're first on the list!
- 什么名单?   - 噢你肯定懂的!
- What list?  - Oh surely you understand!
我们已经找到所有的原身了
We've found all of the originals.
机场总指挥将会一个个把他们逆转换回去
The Commandant at the Airport is going to
deprocess them one by one,
你是第一个, 除非我阻止他
starting with you, unless I stop him.
- 他在唬我们  - 等等!
- He's bluffing.  - Wait!
- 你们在哪里找到原身的?   - 啊, 这我可不能告诉你
- Where did you find the originals?
- Ah, that I can't tell you.
但他们已经搜了一段时间
But they'd been searching for some time
而在我正要上飞机的时候, 我收到了信号
and just as I was about to board the aircraft
I got a signal,
那就意味着他们已经成功了
which meant that they'd been successful.
否则我也不会上来的
Otherwise I wouldn't have come.
如果你不信我, 找盖特威克机场核实一下
Well, if you don't believe me, check with Gatwick Airport.
我估计你知道它的无线电频率吧
I imagine you know its radio frequency?
联系盖特威克机场塔台
Contact Gatwick Air Control.
我已经派了两打人赶过来
I've got two dozen men moving down here
搜索任何有被动过的痕迹的地方
looking for any signs of the soil having been disturbed.
这里有二十个人, 还有五十个志愿者在排查这些机库
There are twenty men here, with fifty volunteers
going through these hangars.
- 总指挥  - 什么事?
- Commandant.  - Yes?
有人在呼叫我们的频率
Someone's crashing our frequency.
- 是谁?   - 我不知道, 先生
- Who is it?  - I don't know sir.
是一个不明身份的电台, 要求同你通话
It's an unidentified station, asking for you.
变色龙总部呼叫盖特威克机场
This is Chameleon Headquarters calling Gatwick Airport.
你能听清吗?
How do you read me?
我是盖特威克机场总指挥
This is Gatwick Airport, Commandant speaking.
我们可以清晰地听到
We are reading you loud and clear.
据我们所知, 你们找到了一些我们感兴趣的东西
We understand you have found some property
in which we have an interest.
- 是这样吗?  - 是的, 我们有那个东西
- Will you confirm? - Yes, we have that property.
- 说明你找到它的地点  - 这有关系吗?
- State where you found it.  - Does that matter?
重要的是我们找到它了, 现在可以毁灭你们了
The important thing is we have found it,
and can now destroy you.
请在听筒旁等待
Please stay by your receiver.
博士肯定在跟他们使诈
The Doctor must be trying some sort of bluff.
但我们却帮不上多少忙
And we are not being much help to him.
- 你把它们放在哪里了?  - 不知道, 就在这里某个地方
- Where d'you think you left them?
- I don't know, I left them in here somewhere.
不管怎样, 不会是变色龙的人拿走了, 因为他们都已经走了
Anyway, none of that Chameleon lot could
have nicked them, 'cos they've all gone.
在这儿, 看!
Here, look!
对了, 我突然想到了
Yeah. You see it suddenly dawned on me -
他们这里这么多车厢是在做什么呢?
what would they be doing with so many coaches?
我怎么没想到?
Why didn't that occur to me?
噢, 你一个人不可能有所有伦敦人的脑子啊
Oh, you haven't got all the brains in London you know.
25个!
Twenty-five!
你看哈, 25辆车, 25个人!
There you are, twenty-five car numbers, twenty-five people!
这里是变色龙总部
This is Chameleon Headquarters.
解释一下你们为什么不愿意说明是在哪里找到那个东西的?
Explain your reluctance to state
where you found the property.
不是不愿意的问题
It is not a question of reluctance.
就说警察还没告诉你
Say the police haven't told you yet.
那个东西在警察手中
The property is in the hands of the police,
他们还没有告诉我之前是藏在哪里的
who have not yet informed me where the hiding place was.
懂了, 请在听筒前等候
Message understood. Please stay by your receiver.
我来接
I'll get that.
航空控制塔台. 请等一下
Air Traffic Control. Hold on a minute.
是那个女孩和你的助理, 她们觉得找到了一个线索
It's the girl and your assistant.
They think they've got a clue.
好, 我尽力拖住他们
Right, I'll try and stall them.
变色龙总部呼叫盖特威克机场, 我们现在开始返回
Chameleon Headquarters to Gatwick Airport.
We are closing down now.
盖特威克机场呼叫变色龙总部, 你们能收到吗?
Gatwick Airport to Chameleon Headquarters,
are you receiving me?
盖特威克机场呼叫变色龙总部, 你们能收到吗?
Gatwick Airport to Chameleon Headquarters,
are you receiving me?
- 盖特威克机场呼叫变色龙总部...  - 关掉
- Gatwick Airport to Chameleon Headquarters...
- Turn it off.
把枪收起来
Put that gun away.
- 他说他们已经找到了我们的原身  - 那他找到了?
- He said he'd found our originals.  - And had he?
不, 他在虚张声势
No, he was bluffing.
继续转化吧
Proceed with the processing.
以后, 你只能听我的命令
In future, take your orders only from me.
你们会大吃一惊的, 等会儿你们就有25个人灰飞烟灭!
You're going to get a surprise
when twenty-five of your people disintegrate!
好可惜啊, 你看不到了
What a pity you won't be able to see it.
护士
The Nurse.
现在看看...你想让我做点什么?
Now then, now... what is it you want me to do?
- 坐下  - 告诉我...
- Sit down.  - Tell me...
在我被转化的过程中, 如果你解体了, 会怎么样?
what happens if ah, you disintegrate
in the middle of my being processed?
我的意思是, 会对我造成什么伤害不?
I mean, will that do me any harm,
比如说, 会不会卡在某个状态与另一个之间之类的
being suspended between one thing and an other,
so to speak...
坐下!
Sit down!
噢, 天
Oh dear.
你应该盯着他的
You should have been watching him.
重新取一个设备
Send for a new unit.
你避免不了你的命运, 只不过推迟了一点
You haven't averted your fate, only postponed it.
终于来了, 博士....
At last. Now Doctor...
你能肯定现在很安全了?
You're quite sure it's safe now?
一切都就绪了吗?
Is everything ready now?
等一下, 长官
Just one moment, sir.
总管, 盖特威克机场又在呼叫我们了
Director. Gatwick Control calling us again.
- 别理他们  - 他们宣称已经找到了原身了
- Ignore them.  - They claim they have found the originals.
他们还是在使诈, 我说了别理他们!
They're bluffing again, I said ignore them!
盖特威克机场呼叫变色龙总部, 你能听到吗?
Gatwick Airport to Chameleon Head Quarters. Do you read me?
还是没用, 先生
It's no good sir.
那好, 我们得给他们个下马威
Very well. We'll have to give them a demonstration.
好了, 警司
Right Super.
Erskine 警长吗?
Sergeant Erskine?
他们已经找到了! 并不是在使诈
They have found them! They weren't bluffing.
可能是他的设备出错了
His equipment could have gone wrong.
那好, 设备可能出什么错?
All right, what could have gone wrong with it?
这个问题得问我们的科学家
That is a question for our scientists.
等他们告诉你设备完全没问题的时候
By the time they tell you
that there's nothing wrong with it,
你们全都解体了——当然除了这位总管
you'll all have disintegrated,
except of course the Director.
闭嘴, 这里没你什么事
Be quiet, this has nothing to do with you.
是, 你完全正确, 这只跟他们俩有关
Yes, you're quite right, it only concerns these two.
我把嘴闭紧
I'll keep my mouth shut.
我们最好联系盖特威克机场台
We'd better contact Gatwick Air Control.
我们跟盖特威克机场没什么事了
We've finished with Gatwick Airport.
如果他们跟我们还有事呢?
And what if they haven't finished with us?
那也是你自己的过失, 对不?
That would be your own fault, wouldn't it.
你跟我说所有的原身都藏好了
You told me that all the originals were hidden.
藏在一个不可能被找到的地方
Where they could not possibly be found
直到有同胞失去生命了
until the life have been drained from them.
你现在才跟我说是你不小心?
Are you now telling me that you were careless?
联系盖特威克机场塔台
Contact Gatwick Air Control.
毁掉收发器
Destroy the transmitter.
好了
All right.
这里是变色龙总部, 呼叫盖特威克机场
This is Chameleon Head Quarters calling Gatwick Airport.
你能听到吗?
How do you read me?
盖特威克机场回复变色龙总部
Gatwick Airport to Chameleon Head Quarters.
我们能清晰地听到你的声音
We are reading you loud and clear.
你们现在能说明在哪里找到的原身吗?
Can you now state where you found the originals?
是在汽车停车场发现的
The originals were discovered in a car park.
为了证明这一点, 我们已经消灭了你们的一员. 一个男人
To prove it, we have already eliminated
one of your personnel. A man.
现在我期望同博士说话
I now wish to speak to the Doctor.
如果我不能马上听到他的声音
Unless I hear his voice immediately,
下一个将被消灭的将是 Blade 机长
the next to be eliminated will be Captain Blade.
放了他!
Release him!
我说放了他
I said release him.
到麦克风那里去!
Get to that microphone!
先放了护士
Release the Nurse first.
我说了我期望同博士说话
I said I wished to speak to the Doctor,
否则下一个将会是 Blade 机长
otherwise the next will be Captain Blade.
博士, 麦克风
Doctor, the microphone.
你没事吧, 亲爱的
Are you quite all right, my dear.
- 嗯, 我觉得没事  - 那就好
- Yes, I think so.   - Good.
总指挥, 我是博士
Commandant, this is the Doctor speaking.
啊, 真松了一口气
Ar, what a relief.
等着, 我去谈判
Stand by while I negotiate.
现在, 我跟你们说说我的条件
Now then, I will tell you my terms.
我可以保障你们会继续存活
I will guarantee your continued existence,
只要你们归还所有被绑架的年轻人
if you will return to Earth
all the young people you abducted.
没用, 他们全都被缩小了
No use. They've all been miniaturised.
- 那就逆转这个过程  - 恐怕那不可能
- Then reverse the process.
- I'm afraid that's impossible,
- 相应的设备在我们星球上  - 他在撒谎
- The equipment for that is on our home planet.
- He's lying.
那些飞机本身就是缩微操作室, 可以双向运作
The planes themselves are the miniaturisation chambers
and they work both ways.
我们能以哪种形式继续存活, 博士?
What kind of continued existence would we have, Doctor?
恐怕只能是你们之前的形态
In your former state, I'm afraid.
你们的科学家得找出其它的方法, 来摆脱你们的困境
Your scientists will have to find
some other way out of your dilemma.
总比死了好
It's better than death.
我们接受
We accept.
好了, 我们接受
All right, we accept.
你们真是愚蠢, 怎么能相信他啊?
You fools, how can you trust him?
小心! 啊...
Look out! Ahh...
- 总指挥, 你还在那边吗?   - 在
- Commandant, are you still there?  - Yes.
谈判已按原定安排成功达成了
Negotiations have been successfully concluded as arranged.
好, 那我就让停车场的人保持原样, 直到你们返回
Good. I'll leave the people in the car park as they are
until you arrive back.
好, 请继续监听这个频率
Good. Please stay listening out on this frequency.
我将让 Blade 机长负责无线电
I am leaving Captain Blade in charge of the radio.
- 你信得过他吗?   - 是的, 我想现在可以了
- Can you trust him? - Yes, I think I can now.
你打算做什么?
What are you going to do?
我要尽力去找到我的三个朋友, 还有督察
I'm going to try and find
my three friends and the Inspector.
- 你知道他们在哪里?   - 是的
- You know where they are?  - Yes.
你带我去找他们. 我会再同你们联系
You will take me to them. I will call you again.
收到
Roger.
好了, Heslington, 赶紧过来
Well, Heslington, flap over.
我们尽我们所能, 让一切快点恢复正常吧
Let's get back to normal as quickly as we can.
在这里, 我不知道具体是哪个
Over here. I don't know which one.
- 博士!   - Jamie! 哈!
- Doctor!  - Jamie! Ha!
见到你还活着可真高兴
I'm glad to see you alive.
什么...你什么意思?
How... how do you mean?
回头再跟你说明吧, 现在赶紧出来
I'll explain to you one day. Well come along out.
你站在那里就像个岗亭里的士兵
You look like a soldier in a sentry box standing there!
坐下
Sit down.
没事, 他是个朋友
It's all right, he's a friend.
现在坐下, 我找找其他人
Now sit down while I find the others.
啊! Crossland 督察, 你在这里啊
Ah! Inspector Crossland. There we are.
接下来, Ben, Polly, 回到盖特威克
Now, Ben, Polly and back to Gatwick.
博士, 第一班飞机已经准备好起飞了
Doctor, the first plane is ready for take-off.
我们已经让所有被转换的人上去了, 包括你的三个朋友
We've got all the processed personnel
including your three young friends aboard.
啊, 很好
Ah, good.
你打算跟我们一起吗, 博士?
Are you going with us, Doctor.?
是的, 我打算跟 Pinto 护士一起
Yes, I'm going with Nurse Pinto.
你呢, 督察?
Are you going Inspector?
不, 我最好在这里再待一会儿, 捋一下头绪
No, I think I'd better stay here just for a while,
to... tidy things up.
- 你准备好了吗护士?   - 是的, 督察
- Are you ready nurse?   - Oh yes, Inspector.
- 我陪你去飞机  - 咱们飞机上见, 护士
- I'll see you to the plane.
- I'll see you on the plane Nurse.
我们的未来会怎样, 博士?
What will our future be Doctor?
只要你们遵守你们的承诺
So long as you keep your side of the bargain,
你们可以毫发无伤地回到自己的星球
you may return to your own planet unharmed.
也许你们的科学家能找到一个方法, 来摆脱你们的困境
Perhaps your scientists will be able to
find some way out of their dilemma.
我也许能给他们贡献一两个点子
I may be able to give them one or two ideas of my own.
好, 好, 我知道, 所有飞机跟你的飞机一样都在待命
Yes, yes, I know,
all flights were suspended as well as yours.
- 你好博士, 都安全地下来了  - 是的, 是的
- Hello Doctor. All down safely.  - Yes, yes.
太好了, 太好了. 我现在得接这个布鲁塞尔的电话
Splendid, Splendid. I'll take that Brussels call now.
- 就还有一件事, 总指挥  - 是, 是, 好的
- There's just one thing Commandant.
- Yes, yes, right.
我们的TARDIS, 我们那个警察亭子
Our TARDIS. Our police box.
(法语)啊, 布鲁塞尔. 是的, 我同意
Ah Bruxelles. Oui, j'accord...
跑道上那个警察亭子
The police box on the runway.
当然, Jean, 帮博士取回他的东西, 行吗?
Of course, Jean, see that the Doctor
gets his property back, will you?
再见博士, 非常感谢你
Goodbye Doctor and thank you so much.
- 谢谢你总指挥  - 再见, 苏格兰小子
- Thank you Commandant.   - Goodbye scottie.
再见, Samantha
Goodbye Samantha.
快来Jamie, 我们必须找到Ben和Polly
Come along Jamie, we must find Ben and Polly
还得找回 TARDIS
and get to the TARDIS.
我还得道个别
I'd better say goodbye.
哦, 那回头见?
Oh, well I'll see you around then?
回头在哪儿?
Around where?
噢, 你知道, 回头...
Well, you know, around...
啊你不会就这样走了吧?
Ah you're not just going off like that?
是, 我必须走. 否则博士...
Aye, I must go. The Doctor'll be...
哦你弟弟马上就会到这里了
Well your brother will be here any moment.
那, 拜拜啦!
Well, ta-ra then!
嘿, 感谢你所做的一切, Jamie
Hey, thanks for everything, Jamie.
我得说再见了
I'll say goodbye.
再见, Jamie
Goodbye Jamie.
这样就行. 给总指挥带个感谢
This will do. My thanks to the Commandant.
非常谢谢你
Thank you every much.
嘿, 博士, 你要去哪儿?
Hey, Doctor, where are you going?
嘿, 回来
Hey, come back.
博士
Doctor.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
做什么? 我在找 TARDIS 啊, 当然了
Doing? I'm looking for the TARDIS, of course.
不要啊, 我们就不能在伦敦待一小会儿吗?
Oh no, can't we stay in London a bit?
是啊, 能回到正常可真是太好了
Yeah, it's good to feel normal again.
正常? 你什么意思, Ben?
Normal? What do you mean, Ben?
就是, 没有怪物, 没有赛博人
Well, no monsters, or Cybermen.
现在这些, 就很正常, 这是我的理解
All this - it's normal. I understand it.
是吗, 变色龙观光游怎么说?
Do you? What about Chameleon Tours?
哦, 这是特殊情况
Oh yeah, that was different!
我对于离开这里倒是很高兴
Oh I'll be glad to get away from here.
你就不能把我们送到一个像1750年那样先进的地方吗?
Can you not land us in a nice civilised place like 1750?
1966年怎么就不先进了?
What's so uncivilised about 1966?
得, 你自己留着吧
Oh, you can keep it!
- 你说这是1966年?  - 是
- Did you say 1966.  - Yes.
现在是几月?
What month is it?
六月. 确切地说, 6月20号
It's July. July the 20th, to be precise.
你想到什么了?
What are you getting at?
你没明白吗, 小姐? 1966年6月20号, 一切开始的时间!
Don't you see, Duchess?
July the 20th, 1966 is when it all began!
我们回到了一开始的起点! 啊, 我觉得....
We're back to when it all started! Well, I think...
这就是说...就好像我们从来没有离开过!
That means it's as... it's as if we've never been away!
你们真的想走, 是吧?
You really want to go, don't you.
这个, 我们不会走的, 博士, 假如你真的需要我们
Well, we won't leave, Doctor, if you really need us.
问题是, 这...这是我们的世界
The thing is, it... it is our world.
是的, 我知道
Yes, I know.
你们很幸运, 我就从来没能回到过我的世界...
You're lucky, I never got back to mine...
好吧, 你们走吧!
All right, then. Off you go!
继续, Ben 可以赶上他的轮船, 成长为一位海军军官
Now go on, Ben can catch his ship and become an Admiral
而你 Polly, 你可以照顾 Ben
and you Polly, you can look after Ben.
我会的
I will.
你们俩注意安全, 好吗?
You will be safe, won't you?
- 我会看着他的  - 我相信你会的, 老兄
- I'll look after him.  - I'm sure you will, mate.
再见博士
Goodbye Doctor.
我们可能某个时候再见, 保重
We might see you sometime. Take care.
你们得快点了, 总指挥的车在等呢
Well you'd better hurry. The Commandant's car's waiting.
看他们走我有点伤感
I'm sad to see them go.
是啊 Jamie, 我也是
Yes Jamie, so am I.
不过, 我们还有事情要做
Well, we've got things to do.
- 什么事情?   - 哦, 我还没告诉他们, 不过...
- What things?  - Well, I didn't tell the others but...
我们的 TARDIS 丢了!
We've lost the TARDIS!
不可能
We can't have done.
刚才还在外面 - 但现在不在那里了
It was outside - it's not there now.
- 你是说, 有人偷走了!   - 我不知道
- You mean somebody's stolen it?  - I don't know,
不过这正是我们要去搞明白的, 快点!
But that's what we're going to find out! Come on!